<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>DAZN Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:29:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/logo.png</url>
	<title>DAZN Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why economic good news is a headache for the Bank of England</title>
		<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/why-economic-good-news-is-a-headache-for-the-bank-of-england/</link>
					<comments>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/why-economic-good-news-is-a-headache-for-the-bank-of-england/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dazn.online.mills.edu/?p=64</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Signs of market growth invite more mortgage agony in the battle against inflation In the long, slow recovery from the financial crisis, the world economy and markets entered a topsy-turvy phase. Bad news sent traders into overdrive, in anticipation of more easy money from central banks. Good news took the wind out of their sails</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/why-economic-good-news-is-a-headache-for-the-bank-of-england/">Why economic good news is a headache for the Bank of England</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Signs of market growth invite more mortgage agony in the battle against inflation</p>



<p>In the long, slow recovery from the financial crisis, the world economy and markets entered a topsy-turvy phase.</p>



<p>Bad news sent traders into overdrive, in anticipation of more easy money from central banks. Good news took the wind out of their sails as financiers feared an end to the cash injections from the authorities.</p>



<p>Now Britain is at risk of a dark repeat of this scenario. But instead of the Bank of England offering the carrot of lower rates and more quantitative easing, this time around it is wielding the stick of more pain for borrowers.</p>



<p>Andrew Bailey, the Governor of the Bank, and his colleagues on the Monetary Policy Committee want to use more expensive money to squeeze demand in the economy and so crush inflation.</p>



<p>It means, ironically, that signs of economic strength invite more agony for mortgage holders, as the MPC fears this is evidence that more must be done to quell inflation.</p>



<p>A slew of economic data published after the Bank’s latest rate rise from 4.5pc to 5pc will worry policymakers who already fear they have not gone far enough to take the momentum out of the economy.</p>



<p>Retail sales volumes in May grew by 0.3pc on the month, a touch slower than 0.5pc in April but much stronger than the drop economists had anticipated.</p>



<p>Families splashed out on summer clothes, outdoor goods, takeaways and fast food, with the hot weather and extra bank holiday for the King’s Coronation encouraging more spending.</p>



<p>At the same time, the influential GFK survey showed consumer confidence increased to its strongest level since the start of 2022, despite the pressure of higher borrowing costs.</p>



<p>The study found a particularly strong rise in households’ predictions for their personal finances over the next year, which suggests they are prepared to keep spending in the face of the Bank of England’s encouragement to cut back.</p>



<p>Joe Staton at GFK calls this “good news” as “consumers are showing remarkable resilience”.</p>



<p>Yet this is not what the Bank of England wants to see. To get inflation back down, it needs consumers to cut back.</p>



<p>At the same time the purchasing managers’ index, a survey of businesses from S&amp;P Global which seeks to provide a forward look of upcoming economic activity, shows sustained growth, led by the services sector.</p>



<p>The index slid to 52.8 this month, down from 54.0 in May. However this is above 50, and so indicates business activity is still growing. Critically, it is also above the 51.0 average of the previous 12 months, suggesting the economy is not slowing as one might have expected after 18 months of steep rises in interest rates.</p>



<p>Chris Williamson, chief business economist at S&amp;P Global Market Intelligence, says its output price index is consistent with inflation falling only to around 6pc from the current level of 8.7pc, and so still three-times the Bank of England’s 2pc target.</p>



<p>“The stubbornly elevated price growth in the service sector suggests the Bank of England will consider its fight against inflation as still a work in progress,” he says.</p>



<p>“However, such rate hikes will clearly add further to the likelihood of a recession later in the year, which is looking increasingly inevitable as collateral damage in the fight against inflation.”</p>



<p>These numbers have driven traders in financial markets to predict ever-higher peaks in interest rates.</p>



<p>The latest forecasts are for the Bank of England’s base rate to hit 6.25pc later this year or early next year, the highest level since 1998.</p>



<p>This comes after a week of data which further underlined the economy’s remarkable resilience, including record employment, soaring pay and an eagerness by employers to hire more staff which means that there are still more than 1m job vacancies on offer.</p>



<p>So far, mortgage borrowers have, similarly, proven resilient to higher rates.</p>



<p>In part, this is because the vast majority have fixed rate loans and are insulated from the immediate impact.</p>



<p>On top of that, households are taking steps to protect themselves from the pain, including by extending the length of their mortgage terms to reduce monthly payments – although this adds to the eventual cost of their loans as interest accumulates over a longer period.</p>



<p>Again this resilience may end up being bad news for borrowers, contributing as it does to the evidence that the Bank still has a way to go to bring inflation down.</p>



<p>Bailey has acknowledged the good news, but caveats it with indications he will raise rates more as required to bring down inflation.</p>



<p>“We’re not seeking to precipitate a recession,” he said on Thursday following the interest rates announcement.</p>



<p>“We’ve got an economy that is much stronger and more resilient than we expected it to be. Part of that is because energy prices have come down so much, which is good news. So we’re not expecting and we’re not desiring a recession. But we will do what is necessary to bring inflation down to target.”</p>



<p>Sources close to Jeremy Hunt also insist he believes a recession is not “necessary” to bring down inflation and that a stronger than expected British economy is something to be celebrated.</p>



<p>“There will be no hesitation whatsoever in Downing Street to do what it takes to get inflation under control,” said one source. “That is a core Conservative value. We will never go into an election without people being confident that a Conservative government knows this.”</p>



<p>Some economists advising the Chancellor say the approach that is needed is patience.</p>



<p>“It may be that we need to be more patient than is usual for monetary policy to bring inflation down,” says Sushil Wadhwani who also used to sit on the nine-strong MPC.</p>



<p>“Remember Friedman’s ‘long and variable’ lags,” he says.</p>



<p>“In this case, the changes in the mortgage market over the last 40 years point to longer lags. In addition, a number of firms hedged their energy costs and other input costs near the peak last year.”</p>



<p>But he believes the prospects for the economy look bleak.</p>



<p>“We are yet to see the full impact of the interest rate tightening that has already happened. The prospect of even more tightening obviously does not bode well for the economy. The higher that rates need to go, the greater the probability of a recession.”</p>



<p>So much for the good news.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/why-economic-good-news-is-a-headache-for-the-bank-of-england/">Why economic good news is a headache for the Bank of England</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/why-economic-good-news-is-a-headache-for-the-bank-of-england/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe: &#8216;Readjusting to UK life was hard&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/nazanin-zaghari-ratcliffe-readjusting-to-uk-life-was-hard/</link>
					<comments>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/nazanin-zaghari-ratcliffe-readjusting-to-uk-life-was-hard/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dazn.online.mills.edu/?p=60</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe: &#8216;Readjusting to UK life was hard&#8217; Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe has said readjusting to life in the UK after six years in an Iranian jail had been slower than she had expected. The British-Iranian national said protests and civil unrest in Iran since her release had kept her story &#8220;fresh on a daily basis&#8221;. &#8220;I resonated very</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/nazanin-zaghari-ratcliffe-readjusting-to-uk-life-was-hard/">Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe: &#8216;Readjusting to UK life was hard&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe: &#8216;Readjusting to UK life was hard&#8217;</p>



<p><strong>Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe has said readjusting to life in the UK after six years in an Iranian jail had been slower than she had expected.</strong></p>



<p>The British-Iranian national said protests and civil unrest in Iran since her release had kept her story &#8220;fresh on a daily basis&#8221;.</p>



<p>&#8220;I resonated very much with what they have gone through,&#8221; she said.</p>



<p>Ms Zaghari-Ratcliffe was arrested in Iran in 2016 on spying charges, which she denied.</p>



<p>She was released in March 2022 and returned to the UK following a sustained campaign.</p>



<p>Ms Zaghari-Ratcliffe made the comments on Friday at Glastonbury Festival, where she was giving a talk about Iranian women&#8217;s rights.</p>



<p>Asked what it has been like readjusting to life in the UK, she said: &#8220;A lot slower than what I thought it would be.</p>



<p>&#8220;Just because early on when I was released, the uprising in Iran happened&#8230; since then I went through stories of many other people who were arrested, and then their stories came out.&#8221;</p>



<p>She discussed the impact of seeing unrest which centred on the death of 22-year-old Mahsa Amini in September while in police custody for wearing her hijab too loosely.</p>



<p>&#8220;My story was all of a sudden so fresh on a daily basis and I couldn&#8217;t get myself out of it &#8211; it was very hard,&#8221; she told the audience.</p>



<p>&#8220;So I think settling down was a lot more complicated and difficult than what I was expecting because of what is happening.</p>



<p>&#8220;But, you know, I can&#8217;t complain. I&#8217;m free and I&#8217;m out, whereas many of my friends are still in prison.&#8221;</p>



<p>During the talk, she said the first names of the friends she was still campaigning to free: Nilufar, Sepideh, Mahvash, Fariba, Morad, Siamak, Emaad and Nargess.</p>



<p>Ms Zaghari-Ratcliffe, from West Hampstead in London, said she felt the continued unrest in Iran was no longer getting the attention it deserved.</p>



<p>&#8220;I think when this whole uprising happened back in September 2022, there was a lot of momentum, but then, of course, the world moves on,&#8221; she said.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="Headinthesand">&#8216;Head-in-the-sand&#8217;</h2>



<p>Her husband Richard Ratcliffe also commented on a damning report by the Foreign Affairs Committee on the Foreign Office&#8217;s handling of hostage diplomacy.</p>



<p>It highlighted examples of &#8220;ministerial clumsiness&#8221; and &#8220;hurtful comments&#8221; in its communication with families.</p>



<p>Mr Ratcliffe described it as an important report.</p>



<p>&#8220;At the moment, cases like Nazanin&#8217;s are reasonably rare&#8230; but they&#8217;re growing, and that growth is something that the government is not really dealing with,&#8221; he said.</p>



<p>&#8220;The head-in-the-sand &#8216;let&#8217;s hope we keep this at a low level&#8217; [approach] and manage it like you would with a really rare illness &#8211; it doesn&#8217;t work.</p>



<p>&#8220;There are a number of countries who are taking hostages, there aren&#8217;t many that make the media, there aren&#8217;t many that the government will acknowledge as hostages or even acknowledge as arbitrarily detained.</p>



<p>&#8220;We&#8217;ll await to see whether the government says &#8216;yes, hands up, we need to get better&#8217; or whether what we get is a &#8216;we&#8217;ll carry on what we&#8217;re currently doing but we&#8217;ll tweak around the edges&#8217;.</p>



<p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve had both in my time&#8230; so let&#8217;s see what comes.&#8221;</p>



<p>The Foreign Office has been approached for comment.</p>



<p>Previously, it said: &#8220;The best interests of British national detainees is at the heart of our consular work and we support and work with their families wherever we can.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/nazanin-zaghari-ratcliffe-readjusting-to-uk-life-was-hard/">Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe: &#8216;Readjusting to UK life was hard&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/nazanin-zaghari-ratcliffe-readjusting-to-uk-life-was-hard/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chelsea &#8216;reject third Man United bid for Mason Mount&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/chelsea-reject-third-man-united-bid-for-mason-mount/</link>
					<comments>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/chelsea-reject-third-man-united-bid-for-mason-mount/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dazn.online.mills.edu/?p=57</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chelsea &#8216;reject third Man United bid for Mason Mount&#8217; Chelsea are reportedly looking for a deal worth £65m in total to allow Mason Mount to leave Stamford Bridge, with the Blues rejecting a £55m offer from Manchester United. Chelsea have reportedly rejected a £55m bid from Manchester United for midfielder Mason Mount, although the Blues are said to have</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/chelsea-reject-third-man-united-bid-for-mason-mount/">Chelsea &#8216;reject third Man United bid for Mason Mount&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Chelsea &#8216;reject third Man United bid for Mason Mount&#8217;</p>



<p>Chelsea are reportedly looking for a deal worth £65m in total to allow Mason Mount to leave Stamford Bridge, with the Blues rejecting a £55m offer from Manchester United.</p>



<p><strong>Chelsea</strong> have reportedly rejected a £55m bid from <strong>Manchester United</strong> for midfielder <strong>Mason Mount</strong>, although the Blues are said to have proposed a counter-offer to their Premier League counterparts.</p>



<p>The 24-year-old last played for the West Londoners in their Champions League quarter-final defeat against Real Madrid on April 18, with a hip injury bringing the player&#8217;s season to a premature end as his side finished 12th in the league standings.</p>



<p>Mount was also unable to be selected for the recent European qualifiers as England faced off against Malta and North Macedonia this month, allowing <strong>Gareth Southgate</strong> to be more experimental in his use of <strong>Trent Alexander-Arnold</strong> in his midfield alongside <strong>Declan Rice</strong> and <strong>Jordan Henderson</strong>.</p>



<p>The Red Devils are said to be searching for reinforcements in their engine room ahead of next season, and according to <em>Sky Sports News</em>, their efforts to lure Mount to Old Trafford have hit another stumbling block.</p>



<p>It is understood that Chelsea have rejected a third offer worth £55m for the former Derby County man, however <strong>Mauricio Pochettino</strong>&#8216;s side are said to be interested in negotiating with United in order to reach an agreement.</p>



<p>The report claims that the Blues have given the Red Devils a counter-proposal of £58m plus £7m in add-ons, although it is unsure whether <strong>Erik ten Hag</strong>&#8216;s men will enter discussions after their third bid was swiftly dismissed.</p>



<p>United are said to be preparing alternative targets should they be unable to secure the services of Mount, with the Old Trafford club keeping an eye on the situation of <strong>West Ham United</strong> midfielder Rice.</p>



<p>With one year left on his current deal at Stamford Bridge, the Chelsea hierarchy will have to sell Mount this summer or risk losing him on a free transfer next year.</p>



<p>The player is said to be keen on departing West London this summer for pastures new after featuring over 190 times for the club, scoring 33 goals and helping the Blues to a historic Champions League title in 2021.</p>



<p>This campaign has been challenging for the 24-year-old, with Mount starting just 20 Premier League matches, his lowest number of games since breaking into the first-team fold during the 2019-20 term.</p>



<p>Mount is understood to have been put off the idea of spending his entire career at Stamford Bridge by recent contract negotiations, with Chelsea unwilling to increase the midfielder&#8217;s wages to a point where he would be one of the club&#8217;s highest earners alongside fellow Englishman <strong>Reece James</strong>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/chelsea-reject-third-man-united-bid-for-mason-mount/">Chelsea &#8216;reject third Man United bid for Mason Mount&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/chelsea-reject-third-man-united-bid-for-mason-mount/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian hockey loses ex-junior star Rajiv Mishra</title>
		<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/indian-hockey-loses-ex-junior-star-rajiv-mishra/</link>
					<comments>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/indian-hockey-loses-ex-junior-star-rajiv-mishra/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dazn.online.mills.edu/?p=54</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Indian hockey loses ex-junior star Rajiv Mishra Rajiv&#8217;s chapter finally came to an end on Wednesday night when the former India junior forward was found dead at his residence in Sarsauli area. (Twitter) Indian hockey failed one of its brightest stars in Rajiv Mishra even before his rise in 1998, thanks to injury mismanagement and</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/indian-hockey-loses-ex-junior-star-rajiv-mishra/">Indian hockey loses ex-junior star Rajiv Mishra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Indian hockey loses ex-junior star Rajiv Mishra</p>



<p>Rajiv&#8217;s chapter finally came to an end on Wednesday night when the former India junior forward was found dead at his residence in Sarsauli area. (Twitter)</p>



<p>Indian hockey failed one of its brightest stars in Rajiv Mishra even before his rise in 1998, thanks to injury mismanagement and sheer neglect of him on the part of the national federation that ran the game then.</p>



<p>And, Rajiv’s chapter finally came to an end on Wednesday night when the former India junior forward was found dead at his residence in Sarsauli area of Varanasi under mysterious circumstances.</p>



<p>He was 46. He is survived by his wife and two children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/indian-hockey-loses-ex-junior-star-rajiv-mishra/">Indian hockey loses ex-junior star Rajiv Mishra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/indian-hockey-loses-ex-junior-star-rajiv-mishra/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Barcelona to begin LaLiga title defence at Getafe</title>
		<link>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/barcelona-to-begin-laliga-title-defence-at-getafe/</link>
					<comments>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/barcelona-to-begin-laliga-title-defence-at-getafe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dazn.online.mills.edu/?p=50</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Barcelona to begin LaLiga title defence at Getafe LaLiga&#8217;s final weekend could be a high-tension climax to the season, with Barcelona visiting Europa League champions Sevilla, Real Madrid hosting Real Betis and Champions League side Real Sociedad hosting Diego Simeone&#8217;s Atletico Madrid. Barcelona will begin their Spanish league title defence away to Getafe on Aug.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/barcelona-to-begin-laliga-title-defence-at-getafe/">Barcelona to begin LaLiga title defence at Getafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Barcelona to begin LaLiga title defence at Getafe</p>



<p>LaLiga&#8217;s final weekend could be a high-tension climax to the season, with Barcelona visiting Europa League champions Sevilla, Real Madrid hosting Real Betis and Champions League side Real Sociedad hosting Diego Simeone&#8217;s Atletico Madrid.</p>



<p>Barcelona will begin their Spanish league title defence away to Getafe on Aug. 13 while Real Madrid visit Athletic Bilbao the same weekend, the Spanish FA (RFEF) said on Thursday.</p>



<p>With the renovation of Barcelona’s Camp Nou already under way, the Catalan giants will host the first Clasico of the season against bitter rivals Real Madrid on matchday 11 (Oct. 29) at the Montjuic Olympic Stadium. Both teams will meet again at Santiago Bernabeu on matchday 32, on the weekend of April 21, 2024.</p>



<p>LaLiga’s final weekend could be a high-tension climax to the season, with Barcelona visiting Europa League champions Sevilla, Real Madrid hosting Real Betis and Champions League side Real Sociedad hosting Diego Simeone’s Atletico Madrid.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu/barcelona-to-begin-laliga-title-defence-at-getafe/">Barcelona to begin LaLiga title defence at Getafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://dazn.online.mills.edu">DAZN Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dazn.online.mills.edu/barcelona-to-begin-laliga-title-defence-at-getafe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
